freehostingbug.com 2013-03-21

# FreeHostingBug Privacy Policy - FreeHostingBug - Free Web Hosting Talk & Reviews

## FreeHostingBug Privacy Policy

This site is owned and operated by Retail Media Concepts LLC. Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. At FreeHostingBug, we want to make your experience with us to be both satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

### INFORMATION FreeHostingBug GATHERS AND TRACKS

We gather two types of information about users:

1\. Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions include but are not limited to receiving our electronic newsletters, requesting or participating in any of our hosted message boards, using our email a friend feature, and from participation in any polls and surveys we may conduct from time to time.

2\. Information FreeHostingBug.com gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our site and hosted forums. This information allows us to better tailor our service to visitors' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because FreeHostingBug.com derives its revenue mainly from sponsorships and advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users. Under no circumstances does FreeHostingBug.com divulge any information about an individual user to any third party.

### CHILDREN AND COPPA

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

### COOKIES

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. FreeHostingBug.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

### USE OF INFORMATION

FreeHostingBug.com uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. FreeHostingBug.com never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.

FreeHostingBug.com creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.
